So both articles we provided you contain the answer but
我们所提供的两篇文章里都包含了答案
let's just take a look at one of the articles.
但是我们只看看其中一篇吧
So Joanna's blog post here.
这是 Joanna 的帖子
Now in this first section, she explains about audio focus.
在第一部分 她解释了 Audio Focus
And further down here,
在下面
she says that you can request the audio focus from the AudioManager class and
她提到你可以从 AudioManager 类中请求 Audio Focus
she provided a link to the method that we can call to request audio focus.
她提供了该方法的链接 我们可以调用该方法来请求 Audio Focus
So, let's navigate there.
我们打开该链接
So, here's the requestAudioFocus method in Android documentation.
这是 Android 文档中的 requestAudioFocus 方法
Now, let's go back to the blog post.
现在我们回到该帖子
In that same sentence, she provides a link on how to release audio focus when
在同一个句子里 她提供了播放完声音后
you're done playing the sound.
如何释放 Audio Focus 的链接
And that takes us to the abandonAudioFocus method
点击该链接 我们就转到了 AudioManager 类中的
within the AudioManager class.
abandonAudioFocus 方法
All right, so we've answered the first two questions so far.
这就回答了前两个问题
We can request audio focus from the Android system by calling
我们可以通过调用 AudioManager 的 requestAudioFocus() 方法
the AudioManager's requestAudioFocus method and then we can play our audio.
来向 Android 系统请求 Audio Focus 然后就可以播放我们的音频了
When we're immediately done playing audio, we can release audio focus
当我们播放完音频后 我们可以通过调用 AudioManager 类中的
by calling the abandonAudioFocus method in the AudioManager class.
abandonAudioFocus() 方法来释放 Audio Focus
Now note that these two methods do have input parameters that you'll need to
注意 这两个方法具有需要传入的输入参数
pass in, but you can shove that in the documentation later when we actually
当我们实际需要使用这两个方法时
need to use these methods.
你可以到时候再去查阅该文档
All right, so on to the third question of what callback should we implement so
对于第三个问题 我们应该实施哪个回调
that we can get notified when the audio focus changes for our app?
以便当应用的 Audio Focus 发生更改时我们会获得通知？
An example of this case is,
举个例子
if a phone call comes in then we need to adjust our audio playback accordingly.
如果有来电 我们就需要相应地调整我们的音频播放操作
Now back in the bog post in the same paragraph, it explains the system
现在回到该帖子的同一段落 这里解释了
may need to temporarily or permanently take the audio focus away from our app.
系统可能需要暂时或永久从我们的应用中拿走 Audio Focus
And so for that we need to create an instance
对此 我们需要创建一个
of the OnAudioFocusChangeListener to listen for
OnAudioFocusChangeListener 实例
these changes on the device so that we can react to them.
来监听设备上的这些更改 以便对其作出响应
So let's navigate to the OnAudioFocusChangeListener interface.
我们转到 OnAudioFocusChangeListener 接口部分
So OnAudioFocusChangeListener is another interface
OnAudioFocusChangeListener 也是一种接口
just like other interfaces that we've used.
和我们使用的其他接口一样
Like OnClickListener and the media players OnCompletionListener interface.
例如 OnClickListener 和 MediaPlayer.OnCompletionListener 接口
So notice that it contains one abstract method that we'll need to implement.
注意 它包含一个需要我们实施的抽象方法
So we need to provide code on what to do when the audio focus changes.
我们需要提供代码 指定当 Audio Focus 发生更改时应该执行什么操作
So for example, if we lose audio focus we should probably
例如 如果我们失去 Audio Focus
stop playing the pronunciation of the word in our app.
我们可能应该停止播放应用中的单词发音
And we can figure out the details of how to handle audio focus changes later.
我们可以稍后再研究下如何处理 Audio Focus 更改
All right, so back to the third quiz question.
回到第三个问题
In order to be notified of changes in audio focus,
为了获得 Audio Focus 更改通知
we need to create an OnAudioFocusChangeListener.
我们需要创建 OnAudioFocusChangeListener
And then we need to implement the onAudioFocusChange callback method.
然后我们需要实施 onAudioFocusChange 回调方法